iconfitness.com 2008-12-16

# ICON Health & Fitness, Inc. Customer Service - Privacy Policy

Manuals  
Replacement Parts  
Check Order Status  
FAQ  
Contact Us  
Product Feedback  
Product Registration  
Privacy Policy  
|  |   

## Privacy Policy

Privacy refers to information that we at ICON Health & Fitness, Inc. ("ICON"), owner of this site, gather about you and the use that we make of it in the course of our business.

ICON collects personally identifying information only during contests, sweepstakes and site membership registration. In addition, information is collected in certain portions of the site in which guests specifically and knowingly provide such information along with content submissions, community postings (i.e., chat or bulletin boards), suggestions, or voting. ICON may use such information for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when guests provide the information). In the event ICON plans to post any such information on a site, guests are provided prior notification of such posting and can decline from having such information posted.

Information submitted at the time of any form of registration may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by ICON. ICON does not share this information with other companies. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use at any time by written request.

_Use of Cookies_

What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while at the site. Cookies make Web-surfing easier by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find cookies at most major Web sites. Cookies help make this site better by showing how and when guests use the site. They do not, however, gather user specific information about persons who use the site. Many content updates and improvements are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This statistical information is most easily tracked with cookies. This information is not shared with any third parties whatsoever. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, it is possible that some areas of this site will not function properly if you do so.

ICON reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying guests of the existence of a new privacy policy. You can send mail with any further questions to us at:

ICON Privacy Policy  
c/o Internet Design Department  
1500 South 1000 West  
Logan, UT  84321
